The Peace Maintenance Brigade was formed twenty years ago.
They stopped war on the continent by reviving a great ancient weapon and using its power.
A great weapon's power?
The Admonisher was a very powerful weapon.
With one shot it could instantly make a whole land perish and kill several hundred people.
What a tremendous weapon...
It seems a lot like Hingistan's giant.
But if they had such a powerful weapon, couldn't they use it to kill the Queen Screaper?
Actually, it was already used.
When that Queen was still alive, the Admonisher crashed into the Queen's seal to break it.
Wow...
Even with such a strong weapon, it couldn't destroy the Queen...