That day, after the experience of completely changing a history of 2000 years,
I hoped for the world that I had known well.
I have been passing my days busily as commander of Monopolis.
Miss Anita, you have worked hard.
I will also return now.
Thanks for your hard work.
I will return after I rest a little.
Miss Anita,
I understand, but
Please do not overexert yourself.
I have been waiting.
I believed in it.
That you would absolutely return.
From the effect of 2000 years ago, those ten days had become lost.
But I believed it,
that we would meet again after passing a long time,
Yurii said it before,
that the future is not decided,
and things will occur in reality if you wish for them.
Therefore, even during that battle, I wished for it.
That we could meet once again,
and that I could be held by you.
Welcome back, my beloved.